http://www.houseofcollars.com/terms

House of CollarsHouse of CollarsHouse of CollarsHouse of CollarsHouse of CollarsHouse of CollarsHouse of CollarsHouse of CollarsHomeShopTermsprivacy policyMoreHomeShopTermsprivacy policyHomeShopTermsprivacy policy
House of Collars Terms of use  Legal NoticeAll notices from House of Collars to You may be posted on our Web site and will be deemed delivered within thirty (30) days after posting. Notices from You to House of Collars shall be made either by regular mail, sent to the address we provide on our Web site, or first class mail to our address at:
Delivery shall be deemed to have been made by You to House of Collars five (5) days after the date sent.Copyright Notice Legal NoticeAll content appearing on this Web site is the property of: House of Collars
Copyright © 1998 House of Collars. All rights reserved. Terms of UseThis site may contain other proprietary notices and copyright information, the terms of which must be observed and followed. Information on this site may contain technical inaccuracies or typographical errors. Information, including product pricing and availability, may be changed or updated without notice. House of Collars reserves the right to refuse service, terminate accounts, and/or cancel orders in its discretion, including, without limitation, if House of Collars believes that customer conduct violates applicable law or is harmful to the interests of House of Collars.Privacy Policy We use security measures to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of the information under our control.  When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information transferred to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.  We do our very best to protect your information. We only contact you if necessary to process your order of if you ask us a question. If you have any questions about the security of your personal information, you can contact us at wolf@cei.net. When contacting us make sure your email system will accept emails from us.  We may retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.  We do not sell or share your information with anyone, unless subpoenaed to do so.    * Cookies are most commonly used to track website activity, thus helping it download faster. When using our site, the server gives you a cookie that acts as your identification card. Upon each return visit to that site, your browser passes that cookie back to the server. In this way, a web server can gather information about which web pages are used the most, and which pages are gathering the most repeat hits.  And your browser can remember the page. Shipping and DeliveryAt this time, House of Collars ships merchandise to locations within the United States and U.S. territories, including Alaska, Hawaii, Puerto Rico, Guam, and the US Virgin Islands. Additionally, House of Collars ships merchandise to Canada and other international locations. The risk of loss and title for all merchandise ordered on this Web site pass to you when the merchandise is delivered to our shipping carrier.InternationalCustoms and import duties may be applied to International orders when the shipment reaches its destination. Such charges are the responsibility of the recipient of your order and vary from country to country. Contact your local customs office for details.
Shipping laws are different in each country. It is your responsibility to check with your Customs office to verify whether the country to which you are shipping permits the shipment of your products. House of Collars is not responsible for any direct, indirect, punitive, or consequential damages that arise from improper international shipping practices.WarrantiesPlease remember these Collars and Cuffs are made of steel or stainless steel. They are jewelry. Misuse in any way is the sole responsibility of the customer.Return PolicyHouse of Collars reserves the right to change its payment procedures at any time without prior notice to you. You item May be return your item within 90 days for any reason for refund less shipping.  If you ordered the wrong size it may be return for free exchange plus shipping.    Start Shopping
Copyright © 1998-2020 House of Collars - All Rights Reserve
